[Music] [Music] The channel we have the most trouble understanding is the life insurance channel, or the agency channel. We face a bit of a problem with that, just because people from the same industry understand it, but people from different industries don't understand it very well. That's why we made this video. These channels are called different profiles in different companies. Suppose, in some companies, they're called AGC Manager, in some they're called Sales Manager, in some they're called Development Manager, in some they're called Unit Manager. And this is a fixed job in which you'll get a fixed salary, plus incentives, bonuses, medical, group insurance. If we talk about incentives, they're very good. And this is a profile in which there are no jobs, you can treat it as a zero-investment business. The less you do, the more you'll earn. It's a zero-investment business, where you don't have to invest anything. You're getting a job as well. If you invest less, you'll do very well.
You can get a salary along with your fees. Now if you work on this profile, then now we talk about the job profile, so what is the geography that you have to do recruitment, this profile is also called recruitment manager in a company, so whose recruitment has to be done, of the agent and advisor, whom in a company, like I said salesman, who is called agency manager, development manager, similarly, an agent is called an agent in some companies, in some companies it is called distributor, in some companies we call it advisor, so in different companies it has to be called by different names and you have to recruit agents, who can be anyone, any businessman, any housewife, any person who wants to work, apart from government employees, we cannot hide government employees, so we can bring a person from any industry who wants to work as an advisor, he gets commission in advice, whatever product he sells.  They have a good commission, this is like an act of God in LIC, if you can understand it a little easily, then the profile is for recruiting it, you should never sell directly, you should never send the policy, instead, if you are going to sell the policy to someone, you should make him an agent, make him an advisor, if you are investing with me, then it is good that you become its return, you can invest and get commission, and whatever premium you are paying for the year, you can also invest it with us, so this profile, camera profile, you should treat it like a business because you might not have thought that you cannot earn so much money, and this is the profile, there is no rocket sense in it, it is like a business and you will also get a fixed salary in it, so thank you very much, you should watch this video and understand the profile, if you want to join this profile, then thank you very much [Music]